[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 7, "question": "You do believe, Mr. President, that a ground war may be inevitable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 8, "answer": "Well, I hope that we achieve a cease-fire.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. President"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["night"]}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "He's still saying that it could go either way but what is your sense on the ground about the likely prospects of a cease-fire and how long will the Israelis give it before committing to a possible ground offensive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "You know, the likelihood of a cease-fire seems to be increasingly elusive the longer this does drag on, and all through the night, we have been hearing the sound of airstrikes, some of them have actually shook the building that we're standing in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RBS", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "But, Arwa, for those who have never been to the Gaza Strip, it's an extraordinary place in the sense that you've got over 1.5 million people crammed into a relatively small area, haven't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "You most certainly do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Arwa", "Gaza Strip"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "How do you see this resolving itself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, there was also an attempt to introduce a cease- fire.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "At what stage does it go over the edge and become an unacceptable form of retaliation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Well, whoever criticized us should suggest an alternative.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "To take the missile and say what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "I think the -- I think critics would say that this particular strategy has proven over the last few years to be an unsuccessful one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "If you believe, Mr. President, that Iran is behind a lot of the Hamas terror activity, as you put it, then what action do you intend to take against Iran?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Not I guess so, I know that is the case, and we are not going to make a war with Iran.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"], "LOCATION": ["Iran", "Iran"], "PERSON": ["Mr. President"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Do you believe, Mr. President, that a ground war may be inevitable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, I hope that we shall achieve a cease-fire.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. President"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "How would you categorize their relationship from your knowledge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "I believe that politics and statesmanship is not just a matter of personal relations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Is he somebody that you trust and do you believe he should now be wielding, if he can, more authority to try and rein in Hamas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "RBR", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hamas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "What are you prepared to concede to Hamas if it gets to negotiation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "We don't put any conditions at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Finally, Mr. President, if there are Palestinians watching this interview who feel helpless, who feel completely poverty-stricken, they have nothing, they see no hope and they now see endless Israeli rockets flying over their heads, perhaps killing relatives and loved ones, what do you say to them to offer proper constructive hope?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "NN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Two things.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. President"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "When you heard Shimon Peres talking, one of the great statesmen of the Middle East, approaching his 90s now, what did you make of what he had to say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "CD", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Well, I think he's right in the fact that first, of course, Israel has the right to defend itself.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Shimon Peres"], "LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "How real do you think that link is between Iran and Hamas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "It is real.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"], "LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "EX", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Why is the world dangling on this precipice, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Well, if you -- put your wonderful map up there, you don't have to, but there are all these powder kegs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "What is your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Well, again, that's crisis management.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Well, we don't -- there's no real crime, there's no identified corruption here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RBR", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Well, the mood is better, but there's some real serious disagreements on taxes and entitlement reform.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Cease-fire, Alan Dershowitz, is it likely?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan Dershowitz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "RB", "NN", "CC", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "What is the difference between Hamas murdering innocent women and children in Israel and Israeli missiles murdering innocent Palestinian women and children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "ERSHOWITZ: It's the essential difference between what constitutes a just war and what constitutes an unjust war.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"], "LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Reza Aslan, your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "I think that's a ridiculous and cynical way of talking about what's going on here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Why should Israel have to put up with just endless rockets being fired into civilian areas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "It should not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "So what should it do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "It should not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", ":"], "qSentId": 329, "question": "But as Shimon Peres said to me, what is the other option?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "There --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Shimon Peres"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "What else do they do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "There is another option.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "What are they saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I would have said six hours ago if you had asked me that I thought that a cease-fire was quite possible and that the principles were in place for a cease-fire.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Let's talk about what is in Israel's benefit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "They may win a -- a few small skirmishes, battles even, but they're not going to win the war overtime, are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Well, let's keep in mind the real history here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Does that justify the rockets?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "No, but it is the real -- it is the reality of what's going on here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Or is there real oxygen of power terror?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "EX", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I've met them and know them well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"], "LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VB", "POS", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "What's the deal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "By the way, let's not pretend that Israel and Hamas are not speaking to each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Did I do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Marijuana.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Did you wake up this morning and have a quick -- you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Well, I probably did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Do you take a lot of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "I think some people have more tolerance, you know, for smoking pot than others.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Colorado"]}, "docId": "121119pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "You and Snoop go to Amsterdam, the Mecca of dope, really, and you both have a load of it and then write some music together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "CC", "NNP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Now we can go to Colorado.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Snoop"], "LOCATION": ["Amsterdam"]}}]